http://www.comcarto.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Privacy Policy:
Comcarto ("Comcarto")
operates comcarto.com and may operate other websites. It
is Comcarto's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Comcarto collects non-personally-identifying information of the
sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference,
referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Comcarto's purpose in
collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand
how Comcarto's visitors use its website. From time to
time, Comcarto may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by
publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Comcarto also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on comcarto.com
blogs/sites. Comcarto only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same
circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that
commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site
where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Comcarto's websites choose to interact
with Comcarto in ways that require Comcarto to gather
personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Comcarto gathers
depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at comcarto.com to provide a
username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Comcarto are asked to
provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to
process those transactions. In each case, Comcarto collects such information only insofar as
is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with
Comcarto. Comcarto does not disclose personally-identifying information
other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with
the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Comcarto may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its
websites. Comcarto may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
However, Comcarto does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Comcarto discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information
only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information
in order to process it on Comcarto's behalf or to provide services available
at Comcarto's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some
of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by
using Comcarto's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to
them. Comcarto will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated
organizations, as described above, Comcarto discloses potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or
when Comcarto believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of Comcarto, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered
user of an Comcarto website and have supplied your email address, Comcarto
may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to
date with what's going on with Comcarto and our products. If you send us a request (for
example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us
clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Comcarto takes all
measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of
potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser
provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Comcarto uses cookies to
help Comcarto identify and track visitors, their usage of Comcarto
website, and their website access preferences. Comcarto visitors who do not wish to have
cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before
using Comcarto's websites, with the drawback that certain features
of Comcarto's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Comcarto, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that Comcarto goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the
assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that
any acquirer of Comcarto may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this
policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to
compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among
other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by Comcarto and does not cover the use of cookies by any
advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Comcarto may change
its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Comcarto's sole
discretion. Comcarto encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to
its Privacy Policy. If you have a comcarto.com account, you might also
receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in
this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Latest Blog Entries
Commonly Overlooked Liabilities to look out for When Purchasing Land
Reasons to Hire a Geotechnical Engineer
How to Choose an Environmental Consultant
Solutions
Industry NewsRisk-Based Fatigue Design Considering Inspections and MaintenanceUse of the Probability Transformation Method in Some Random Mechanic ProblemsProbabilistic Inference for Structural Health Monitoring: New Modes of Learning from DataLocal System Modeling Method for Resilience Assessment of Overhead Power Distribution System under Strong WindsGlobal Decoupling for Structural Reliability-Based Optimal Design Using Improved Differential Evolution and Chaos ControlCategories
Environmental Consultant
Search
Copyright © Comcarto. 2020 All Rights Reserved. | Privacy Policy
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
